All right. So now for the fun part,
现在到了比较有趣的部分了
what we're going to do in this video is we're actually going
在本视频中 我们将向用户
to ask the user for permission,
请求权限
set their location and then show real time data here rather than just this dummy data.
设置位置信息 然后显示实时数据 而不是这些虚拟数据
So the very first thing we're going to do,
首先
is we need to import a few things,
我们需要导入一些内容
location and permissions which are both coming from expo,
导入 Location 和 Permission 都来自于 expo
and then also calculate direction which is coming from utils/helpers.
然后导入 calculateDirection 来自于 utils/helpers
So the very first thing we want to do is let's make a method called setLocation.
首先创建一个方法 叫做 setLocation
This method is going to be called when we have
当我们确认获得了位置信息访问权后
confirmed that we have the correct permissions to get their location.
就会调用该方法
So what we're going to do here is we're going to call Location.watchPositionAsync.
我们将调用 Location.watchPositionAsync
And what we want to do is pass this a few different options.
传入几个不同的选项
We will say enable high accuracy to be true because we
输入 enableHighAccuracy 设为 true
care about the very small changes in the phone's location.
因为我们很关心手机位置的细微变化
Time interval, we're going to set to one,
timeInterval 设为 1
and distance interval, we're going to set to one.
distanceInterval 设为 1
The reason we're doing this is just this is how often it updates,
这么设置的原因是这是更新频率
and I don't really know the minimum amount,
我不知道最低频率是多少
so I just put one because we want this to update,
所以直接输入 1 因为我希望更新这些信息
we want their location update as quickly as possible.
希望能尽快更新用户的位置信息
So now what we're going to do is we are going to pass a callback function as
现在传入一个回调函数
the second argument to watchPositionAsync
作为 watchPositionAsync 的第二个参数
because whenever the position of the phone changes,
因为每当手机位置变化时
this function is going to get called,
就会调用该函数
and we are going to get past the phones coordinates.
我们将传入手机的坐标
So now what we can do is we'll come in here and we'll say newDirection equals,
在这里输入 newDirection = calculateDirection
we'll just calculate the direction passing it, coords.heading.
传入 coords.heading
So this is going to return us like North-North-East, something like that.
这个将传入东北方向等等
And then now, we will also get the direction from this.states.
我们还将从 this.state 获取 direction
And then what we will do,
我们将在后面的视频中解释
and the reason we're doing this is you will see in a future video,
这么设置的原因
but we're going to do that for now,
暂时先这么设置
and now what we want to do is setStates,
现在输入 this.setState
and what we are going to do here,
我们将在这里
is we're going to update state with state with the coordinates,
使用坐标更新状态
with the status of granted and with the direction being the newDirection.
status 为 granted direction 为 newDirection
So now we have setLocation but what we want to do
我们设置好了 setLocation
before that is inside of component did mount,
但在此之前 我们需要转到 componentDidMount 中
we need to make sure that we have
确保获得正确的权限
the correct permissions or we need to ask the user for these permissions.
或需要请求用户授予这些权限
So what we can do is we can call permissions.getAsync,
我们可以调用 permissions.getAsync,
and the permission we care about is permissions.LOCATION, all caps.
需要获得的权限是 permissions.LOCATION
And then, what's going to happen is we will be
然后传入一个对象
past an object which has a status property.
具有 status 属性
If the status, as you've seen before,
正如之前看到的
is granted, then what we want to do is call setLocation.
如果 status 是 granted 则调用 setLocation
So if we ask them permission, they grant the permission,
如果我们请求权限后 用户授予权限
or we've already been granted permission,
或已经被授予权限
then go ahead and set the location.
则设置位置信息
If not, then what we want to do is say setStates and just update the status.
如果不是这种情况 则调用 setStates 并更新 status
If there is any issue here,
如果出现任何问题
what we want to do is let's catch that error,
则 catch 这一错误
and then we will say counsel.worn.
然后输入 console.warn
Let's say Error getting Location permission to show the error.
“Error getting Location permission:” 显示该错误
And then we will update setStates,
然后更新 setState
and we will just say our status is undetermined.
输入 status: ‘undetermined’
All right, so let's see if this is working.
看看是否可行
I reset all of the settings in my simulator
我在模拟器中重置下所有设置
just because I wanted to show from a fresh start of what would happen.
以便从头显示所发生的情况
And super big buzzkill,
出现了很严重的错误提示：
I can't find variable permissions because we called
Can't find variable: Permissions because we called
this permission instead of permissions and now all of this should work.
因为这里是 permission 而不是 of permissions 现在应该可行了
All right, got it, expo.
Got it expo
All right, so now let's go to the live tab, oh, buzzkill.
转到 Live 标签页 很扫兴
So you'll notice here that we are getting
系统提示
this screen saying we need to enable location services.
我们需要启用位置服务
The reason we're getting this is because when the come on amounts,
出现这个屏幕是因为
we are saying hey,
当组件加载时 我们会问
do we have permission?
我们有权限吗？
Like get the permission of these location services.
获得这些位置服务的权限
If it's granted already,
如果已经授予权限
then set the location.
则设置位置信息
If it's not granted,
如果没有授予
then just set the status to whatever it is.
则将 status 设为任意状态
So we're never actually asking them for permission.
因此我们没有实际地请求权限
So that's what we're going to do in the next video,
这将是下个视频的任务
is to learn how to ask the user for permissions. So that way.
也就是如何向用户请求权限
Here, if it's not granted,
这样的话 这里如果没有授予权限
we can ask them permission and we can also
则可以请求权限
ask them permission when they click on this button right here.
此外 当用户点击这个按钮时 也可以请求权限